David, we're back! I'm so sorry it took so long.
戴维 我们回来了 很抱歉耽误了这么久
Are you okay?
你还好吗
-Bartell did it. It's to keep the bugs out.-You know, David is quite the young man. He has set the bar very high for future hostages.
-巴尔特把虫子挡在了外面-你知道的 戴维是个很安静的年轻人 他为未来的人设定了很高的标准
Now, let me guess. You have failed to break the contract and have returned for combat!
现在让我来猜猜 你没有违反合同并且返回去辩论了一番
No! Very much the opposite.
没有 完全相反
That glow. Lindworm flame?
林德虫的火焰
Mm-hmm. The contract is broken. Your exile is over!
嗯 合同解约了  你们的流放结束了
You can finally leave this place and move into No Elf's Land.
你可以离开这里去没有精灵的地方
Oh.
奥
"Oh"? What do you mean, "Oh"?
奥 你奥是什么意思
Well, uh, we were so angry about being exiled, we never thought about actually leaving this place.
这个 额 我们确实因为流放感到很生气 但还真没想过会离开这个地方
But what about No Elf's Land?
但哪里才是没有精灵的地方
I don't know. Do you still want it?
我不知道 你还想去吗
Really? You'd cede your ownership rights just like that?
真的吗 你会那样放弃你的所有权吗
No contract, no lease, no anything?
没有合约 没有流放 什么约束也没有
Well, we have our own way of sealing deals.
好吧 我们有自己的销售方式
Oh. Good.
哦 太好了